[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
TAKE CHARGE OF MY HEART
Okay.
I will
save you, Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
Then move into my place tomorrow.
Tomorrow? That soon?
I need to tell my sister and brother.
Give it a rest already.
It's not fair.
I wanted to eat that one.
Just eat whatever.
-Hide. -Why should I hide?
-I said just eat whatever! -But I picked that one!
Hey, Yong-gi!
You're stressing me out.
Huh?
-What are you doing here? -Our baby sister is here!
For our baby sister…
Here, have this. It's the most expensive one.
Sweet! It looks good.
-Have you eaten? -Yeah.
What about you guys?
She wanted ice cream first.
You haven't eaten?
-We ate earlier. -You call that dinner?
You scarfed it down. What's your problem?
-Come on, guys. -Jeez.
I'm here to pick you up.
Is anything bothering you?
Well…
No, I just…
I can't believe this is really happening.
And I feel bad for lying to my sister and brother.
The company's giving you a studio? Just like that?
Yeah.
I knew our Bo-bae would make it big someday.
In three months, Na Ji-hye will be married,
I'll be in Daejeon, and this home will be gone.
Bo-bae, it all worked out, huh?
You're not making this up, are you?
Come on. Why would I make that up?
I guess that's true.
Thank you for making this difficult decision.
If it weren't for you, Mr. Baek
would've been in grave danger.
Right.
As for your role, Ms. Na Bo-bae,
it is strictly limited to charging.
Please keep that in mind.
I will.
Well… Mr. Yoon?
Yes?
Well, it sounds like Mr. Baek Ho-rang holds a very high position.
What exactly does he do?
He's the senior managing director of TS Resort.
TS?
That's a huge company.
Senior managing director?
Doesn't that basically make him a chaebol?
More precisely, he's a third-generation chaebol.
This is Mr. Baek Ho-rang's house?
Yes.
You'll be staying here for the next three months.
We meet again.
We do indeed.
You shoved me into a corner yesterday.
I thought you didn't want to see me.
Well, it's just that…
I didn't really know how to explain it.
And you seem just fine.
So petty.
Your house is super nice.
Can I take some pictures? For research.
No, you can't.
I won't show anyone. I'll never see a house like this again.
If any photos get leaked, I'll sue you.
So go ahead and take them.
That's spot on.
What is?
You always see them in dramas.
The man who shut himself off, scarred by a painful past,
only to be changed by true love:
the rude-ass third-gen chaebol heir.
Sorry, but this is reality, not a drama.
And "rude-ass"? What do you--
Stop looking around and come here.
This is as far as you're allowed.
In other words, don't wander off anywhere else without…
Looks like you eat pretty well.
My housekeeper keeps it stocked for me.
So chaebol have housekeepers, huh?
How did you explain who I am to--
Do I really
have to explain?
Well, I mean,
we'll be running into each other a lot.
That won't be necessary. Don't worry.
Our arrangement
stays strictly between us.
Why did you put that on?
Take it off.
This is my room.
It's bigger than my living room.
Wow, this bed is massive.
Feel free to lie down.
What?
If we're going to have physical contact, we'll have to share a bed at times.
Why would we have physical contact in bed?
Would you rather do it in public?
Actually…
I need…
a recharge now.
What are you doing?
My room.
I want to see my room.
Wait.
I want to see my room. Why are we back outside?
Huh?
This is where you'll be staying from now on.
What?
But this is
a storage room.
This is your room.
Why put me here when you have that nice…
Charging my heart is the whole point of our contract.
It's exactly ten meters from here to my room.
So charging shouldn't be a problem.
There's no need for us to live together.
-But-- -Come on.
Let's go over our contract.
Well…
-If you want, I can redecorate-- -I do.
Have a seat.
Look it over.
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR BAEK HO-RANG
What?
This whole thing is the contract?
My life is at stake here.
-This is the bare minimum. -How am I supposed to read all this?
I've only listed my terms so far.
You can add yours now.
"Na Bo-bae shall charge Baek Ho-rang's artificial heart
every morning at 7:30…
by holding his hand."
I'm never up before 10:00, especially after writing all night.
I work in an office. I start at 8:30.
This is the only way I can fully charge and stick to my morning routine.
"Under normal circumstances,
Baek Ho-rang shall not request any method of recharging other than hand-holding."
"However, if the battery level falls below 10%,
Na Bo-bae shall, without exception, through close physical contact…"
"Close"?
What constitutes "close physical contact"?
Contact between mucosal surfaces.
What?
Well…
Like kissing or…
something beyond that.
In any case, it only applies in emergencies
when the battery drops below 10%.
Oh.
I mean, we'll be living together.
It's not like the battery will ever drop below 10%, right?
I agree.
It's just a formality. Don't worry.
And I have no desire
to have "close" physical contact
with you, Ms. Na Bo-bae.
That's great.
If it weren't for my script,
I wouldn't even share a table with you.
If you say so.
Where do I add my terms?
DO ONE ROMANCE BUCKET LIST ITEM EACH WEEK
"Romance bucket list"?
There are a few dates I want to write into my script.
I'm just a teensy bit weaker on the romance front,
so I wanted to experience it before I write it.
It's nice and clear. Share the list with me later.
Sure.
The next one is right below it.
"During this agreement, neither Na Bo-bae nor Baek Ho-rang
shall see anyone of the opposite gender,
and shall be sincere with one another."
I wasn't planning on seeing anyone anyway.
You sure you don't have a boyfriend?
I told you, I don't.
You're all I have.
What I'm saying is…
I didn't mean you're all I have in that way.
As a man.
You're the only man I've got?
Okay, I get what you mean.
Yeah.
I get it.
-We're all set now, right? -Yes.
One more thing.
I'll be the one to initiate charging.
Whether it's holding hands, hugging,
or close physical contact.
Since my body is the charger, I'll decide when and how it happens.
All right.
I'll revise it accordingly.
Oh, right.
After we sign,
we'll test the charging rate.
Is that okay?
Yes, that's fine.
We'll have to hold hands, hug,
and maybe…
even do more.
I mean, it's just a test.
It's fine.
All right.
I'll take that as a yes.
MY SIS
Hey, Ji-hye.
Hey, are you at the studio?
How is it? Is it okay?
Oh, this place?
It's really nice.
It's spacious, and it's got all the latest equipment.
And it's got an amazing view.
Since the TV station arranged the studio for you,
we probably shouldn't go, right?
You okay living alone?
Of course I am.
I see this as my last chance.
I really want to make it.
I want to see my name on a drama,
and I want to proudly call myself a drama writer.
I don't want to feel small and ashamed of my scripts anymore.
Tell me if anyone looks down on you. They won't get away with it.
Don't worry about anything else. Just focus on writing, okay?
Now all you have to do is become a star writer, Na Bo-bae.
All right.
Is it Bo-bae?
Go away.
Bo-bae! Our Bo-bae is the best!
-Stop! -You're Korea's best writer!
I said go away. Go.
Ji-hye, I have to go. I need to work on my script.
Okay. Hey, Bo-bae.
Yeah?
Give it your best shot.
But if things get tough, you can always come back.
You know that, right?
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
That's right.
I should at least give it my best shot.
ROMANCE DRAMA WRITING TECHNIQUES
Charging starts at 7:30 every morning. It's already 7:40.
I'm sorry.
Morning charging is just holding hands, right?
Be on time from now on. I can't stand people breaking the rules.
It's clearly stated in the contract.
Fine.
Here.
I'll come straight home after work. We'll test the charging rate tonight.
Are you crazy?
I told you to wait six months!
We just signed a contract last month. Why'd you go and sign another?
Are you trying to get caught?
-My head's killing me. -My apologies.
I guess our VP was in a hurry.
TS HOTEL FOOD SUPPLY CONTRACT
A mistake like this? Really?
Yoon Dong-seok!
Do you have any idea how important this is?
Imagine if my husband finds out.
You won't be leaving in one piece!
My deepest apologies, ma'am.
Hey, Baek. You'll get wrinkles from frowning.
"Hey, Baek"? Is that any way to address your mother?
You think this doesn't concern you?
Baek Ho-rang's successor announcement is on hold.
This is our chance to get ahead.
If they find out we messed with the money,
we're toast.
As you can see,
Mr. Ji Eun-ho landed his first lead role with Ms. Na's debut work, Wistful Youth.
Well, you're a fan.
That's why you're so nice about my work.
That damn romance.
So that was Ji Eun-ho.
He only backed out of the meeting
because Ms. Na was hospitalized.
If we can get Ms. Na on our side first…
Hold on, sir.
-Please don't. -His schedule is full.
If you can schedule a meeting later…
Wait, sir! You can't…
Hey.
You think you own this place?
Sir, Mr. Baek has an appointment shortly.
If you could set up--
I was passing by and thought I'd drop in.
Thought I'd come see my dear cousin.
It's your birthday soon.
Want anything?
Since when do you care about my birthday?
Get out. I'm busy.
Come on. Everyone here is busy.
You always act like you're so important and busy.
Hey, Kim.
Get me an iced Americano. Extra shot.
He's Mr. Yoon.
Don't bring it.
If you want coffee, go to a café. If you want to have fun, go to a club.
No one's got time for you here.
Mom.
I'm certain.
He doesn't know yet.
Your name came up during the table read with Director Yeom.
-Is she messing with me? -So I thought I'd text. Good luck!
Thanks, Ju-hee… Hope your drama blows up…
I'm the one who needs to blow up.
This is seriously driving me nuts.
No.
I don't have time for this.
I've been waiting for you, Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
"Romance Bucket List."
"Drink together until late at night."
"Late-night walk by the Hangang River."
"Nighttime theme park date."
Did I overdo the whole nighttime thing?
-Do we have to do them in order? -No.
That doesn't matter.
DO A CHAEBOL FLEX
"Chaebol flex"?
What's this?
My female lead's a third-gen chaebol facing an assassination threat.
The male lead is assigned as her bodyguard.
As they slowly fall in love--
Just the bottom line.
I heard you were a chaebol. Let's see you splash the cash.
Isn't that kind of cliché and childish?
Why is every drama about chaebols
when there aren't even a hundred conglomerates in Korea?
Go ahead. Laugh all you want.
I know the chaebol fantasies in romance dramas
are far-fetched and childish.
Still,
they're fun.
Enough to keep people coming back.
It doesn't matter if it's cliché and childish.
When you're watching something fun, you forget everything else.
The hardships, the loneliness, the pain.
When you're watching something really fun, it whisks you away to another world.
Do you know how incredible that is?
Look, I'll do everything you need. The tests, the actual charging, all of it.
In return, I want your full cooperation with my romance.
Of course. We have a contract.
Let's start the charging rate test. And then we'll cross one thing off
your bucket list.
RUBBER GLOVE
Isn't it done yet? It's been about ten minutes.
HO-RANG'S ROOM STORAGE ROOM
PORTABLE CHARGER
So it does charge 1% every ten minutes.
All right. Next.
CHARGING RATE TEST
So? How much did it drop?
When you're in the garage,
charging only works as far as my room.
BACKYARD GARAGE
And it seems to drop 1% every 15 minutes.
If we're close,
charging seems to take only seven or eight minutes.
It's not very consistent, is it?
It seems to vary with my condition and heart rate.
We'd have to test different levels of physical contact…
to know for sure.
Oh.
Different levels of physical contact. Right. We should test that.
Holding hands?
All right.
Holding hands brings it up by 5%.
Next would be…
Let's try hugging.
Yeah. Sure.
Did I jump in too fast?
Why is it beeping?
A heart rate of 100?
It's nothing!
I mean, this…
It probably charged up too fast.
Hugging increases it by 10%.
Well,
I guess
next would be
kissing, right?
As for kissing,
I don't think we need to do that now.
-Right? Yeah. -Yes.
I wasn't that curious anyway.
I did kind of prepare myself for it.
But if we don't, we don't.
-Sounds like you want to. -No way.
Why would I? Not at all.
You should get that.
Yes, Mr. Yoon.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay. I'll check. All right.
Why are you grabbing my hand like that?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I thought we were doing your bucket list today.
Oh.
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR BAEK HO-RANG
Yes.
I just got off the phone with Mr. Baek.
The night air feels so nice.
It's humid.
Damn it.
If this were a drama, now would be the perfect time to hold his hand.
Should I say it's for the script and do it?
Is this really on your bucket list?
Sorry?
We're just walking. Even in a drama, this would be boring.
Well…
Night walks have a certain romance, you know.
Like, there's this tingly tension
when you're almost touching, but not quite--
That was close.
I'm fine.
I'm not.
I don't think I got hit,
but my heart rate's way up.
That can't be good for my heart.
It's dark out and he didn't even ring--
What's the damn bell for, decoration?
What if Mr. Baek got hurt in an accident this late at night?
Does he think he owns the Hangang River?
Why are you…
Enough walking. Let's grab a bite and head home.
Does he only care about himself?
Romance, my ass.
A romance? With a guy like him?
All right. Here's your food.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Looks yummy.
There's so much. You sure you don't want any?
No, I'm good.
You've never had chicken feet before?
How can I eat something that looks like this?
It might not look appetizing, but it's really good.
-Like pig trotters. -I don't eat those either.
They've been serving chicken feet for three generations.
This is seriously good.
It's good for your health too.
It's practically medicine.
How can something this spicy and salty be medicine?
-You're just fooling yourself. -Yeah, I am.
So what? It still tastes good.
Seriously, it's so good.
Look. If you dip it in the sauce like this…
Want some, huh?
No way. I don't want any.
Then
just try the end.
-I'll cut it off for you. -In that case…
No foot shape.
Seriously.
Here.
Isn't it good?
It's good, right?
I guess it's not bad.
Do you know how they make these boneless chicken feet?
No, I don't.
The owner gnaws the bones out one by one, like this.
That's how he makes them boneless.
How's everything? Good?
Enjoy.
He's got strong teeth.
I was just kidding.
All right, then. Go on in.
Bet you'll sleep well tonight after that big meal.
Good night.
Don't forget about the hospital tomorrow.
The Hangang River date.
Better do it before I forget. Quick.
Hye-ju and I-hyeok walk
side by side along the Hangang River.
THEIR HANDS ALMOST BRUSH
THE TWO ARE ACUTELY AWARE OF EACH OTHER
Ma'am.
(HOLDING HER IN HIS ARMS)
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Are you sure you don't need to go to the hospital?
I'm okay.
(TREMBLING)
(STARTLED)
You're bleeding!
I-HYEOK HIDES HIS WOUND AS IF IT'S NOTHING
As long as you're not hurt, I'm fine.
I-HYEOK GAZES AT HYE-JU WISTFULLY
That's it. That's more like it.
He likes her,
so he doesn't care if he gets hurt as long as she's okay.
I'm fine.
I'm not.
I don't think I got hit.
That can't be good for my heart.
Real life is nothing like the dramas.
How about changing your sleep pattern?
I was in the zone last night.
It was like I was possessed.
They say great writers write a set amount every day,
no matter how they feel.
Yeah, well, I'm still just a lousy rookie writer.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
I'll handle it.
Ma'am.
-Yes? -Excuse me.
May I see your phone?
Why?
I heard a camera click.
Just making sure you didn't take a photo of us.
What?
Why would I take a photo of you people?
I'm just being careful.
-Please excuse me. -No!
What's Mr. Yoon doing?
He's checking whether she took a picture of me.
What? Why would she take a picture of you?
She could be a paparazzo or a reporter in disguise.
What?
Listen, we're not even allowed to use our phones while we're working!
Isn't this a bit much?
Keep your opinions to yourself.
People are watching. Talk to her somewhere quiet.
No!
Sir?
Sir!
Seriously, I swear I didn't take any photos.
Look.
We're not allowed to use our phones while we're cleaning,
but I was texting my daughter.
That's why I couldn't show him.
Do you think he'll report me?
They've gone to report me, right?
Just explain what happened. I'll talk to them too.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
I didn't take any photos. He just came up to me.
You took off like something happened, yet here you are,
just chilling.
Go check on the cleaner.
Yes, sir.
I checked her phone. There were no photos of you.
Mr. Yoon, go check it.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Do you always go around accusing people and saying whatever you want?
That's OCD, paranoia, or something like that.
It's your problem.
Well,
now that you're here, have a seat.
I heard you and Ho-rang tested the charging rate.
Since it's not exactly normal for a person to charge an artificial heart,
I'd like to run a few tests to make sure nothing's wrong with you.
Right.
We're here for different tests.
Did you have to call us in together?
I don't want to be around some power-tripping narcissist either.
Can I go get my tests now?
-Well… -Ms. Na.
You don't know my story, so watch what you say.
Don't act like your bad manners come with some backstory.
You think you're some paragon of virtue?
It's always the ones with character flaws who ask that.
-Ms. Na Bo-bae! -What, Mr. Baek Ho-rang?
Excuse me, you two.
-Let's do the tests! -Where do I go?
Did you have heart surgery? That's a big scar.
I was struck by lightning when I was a kid.
It's from that.
-Lightning? -Yeah. Pretty unusual, right?
Yes, it is.
I checked, but there were no photos of you.
No deleted photos either.
Make sure to apologize to her and compensate her properly.
Yes, sir.
Shall I call her back?
Don't bother.
We'll go separately.
Mother, are you asleep?
Stepmom.
Hey, lady.
I can't visit for a while.
I've found something more interesting than watching you.
Who is this woman?
They looked pretty close. Maybe she's his girlfriend?
Baek Ho-rang's girlfriend?
Got any other photos of her?
No, not yet.
Follow him around the clock.
-Okay? -Yes, sir.
And find out more about her.
Yes, sir.
Cheers.
Going all out already? You just had your appendix out.
I'm fine now.
Excuse me, could we get some chopsticks?
Gonna drink till I drop. Don't stop me.
What if Ji-hye gets mad at me for letting you drink?
Your sister really scares me.
It's okay. I moved out.
Huh? When?
Yesterday.
No way. Damn.
Why didn't you tell me?
-Well… -Yeah?
Actually…
You're out of your mind.
What if your sister and brother find out you lied?
Your sister's gonna kill you if you keep this up.
No. Listen.
Say I spend three months with Mr. Baek,
fulfill our contract, and finish my bucket list.
Then I work it into my script.
-Work it in. -Then I renew my writing contract.
-Renew it. -Then…
-It won't be a lie anymore. -What if they don't renew it?
Your brother's moving to Daejeon. Your sister's moving in with her husband.
And that chaebol will kick you out once the contract's up.
Then what? You'll have nowhere to go.
If they don't renew my contract,
I'll have to move back in with my parents.
No plan, huh?
You're driving me up the wall.
I have it worse.
That chaebol whose name means "tiger." What if he finds out about your powers?
You said he has no idea why you can charge his heart.
He doesn't get zapped when I touch him. I don't think he'll ever find out.
He just doesn't know yet.
What are you gonna do
if you get angry or too excited and blow out the lights?
-You think so? -"You think so"?
Hey, don't you know rich snobs sue at the drop of a hat?
What if he sues you for lying about your powers?
You're right.
I have to make sure he never finds out.
What time is it?
Huh? We have to go.
Hey, Bo-bae. Wake up.
Hey, wake up. We have to go.
Wake up.
Sorry. We're leaving. Just a second.
DIRECTOR YEOM MIN-KYU
Well, if it isn't my favorite director!
Right now?
Yes.
I had a few drinks, but I'm not that drunk.
No.
Yes, I'll be right there.
What am I going to do with her? Seriously.
Hey, wake up. We really have to go. Damn it.
Crap. What am I supposed to do with her?
Someone's calling her.
You little punk! Perfect timing.
Hey.
Damn it. Seriously.
-Eun-ho! Hey. -Ms. Cho.
Eun-ho, thank you so much.
I should take her home,
but Director Yeom suddenly put me to work.
-Right. -Yeah.
I know you two are close, so…
Yes, I'll take care of Bo-bae.
Okay. Thank you so much.
No problem.
Oh, that's right.
You know Bo-bae doesn't like being touched, right?
-Yes. -Don't try to support her.
Touch her through her clothes if you need to.
Just wake her up and get her home, please.
-Yes, got it. -Please look after her.
Bye.
Wake up already, Na Bo-bae!
Go, damn it.
Jeez, I'm off, then.
All right.
Bo-bae.
Damn it.
I mean…
Just because he makes a lot of money and has a fancy business card,
does he think he can treat a cleaner however he wants?
Wow, she's really drunk.
Why, you…
Damn it.
Bo-bae, let's go.
You little…
Let's go. Get up.
Bo-bae, come here.
Wow!
Bo-bae!
What if the battery dies? Why isn't she back yet? Damn it.
I used to eat this a lot as a kid.
You know what? He was my favorite.
He can generate electricity too, and he's super strong.
Me too.
Bet that's why Pikachu is everyone's favorite.
So you should stop hiding it from me and…
What's this?
RUBBER GLOVE
"Rubber glove"?
Forget it. I'm not answering.
This douchebag. I can't stand the sight of him.
Go on. So you like Pikachu too?
Yes.
Very much.
I didn't know Pikachu was this popular.
The person you're calling is unavailable.
Please call back later.
She's not picking up?
PORTABLE CHARGER
Come home right now.
Get within a ten-meter radius of me!
Read it.
Don't tell me…
Is she not gonna come back at all?
Twenty-five hours since separating from Na Bo-bae.
Dead.
DEAD
It's all just pointless worries.
I need to clear my mind of distracting thoughts and worries.
As you breathe in, feel positive energy fill you.
As you breathe out, release all the negative energy.
When you exhale, let go of the person troubling you.
Mr. Baek Ho-rang. A power-tripping narcissist.
You'd be dead without me.
Scared? Anxious? Losing your mind?
No!
What the…
Damn it.
Bo-bae, you live here now?
Yeah.
Darn it.
This thing's just like its owner. Damn it.
Seriously…
Bo-bae, I don't think this is the right place.
It's way too big. Look again. Are you sure?
It's the right place. Baek Ho--
Our arrangement
stays strictly between us.
Actually, no.
It's not here.
Where is it? I'll take you home.
No!
It's the house next door. Right next door.
I'm so drunk, aren't I?
Here. This is it.
I'll head in. Go on home, Eun-ho.
-I'll go after you go-- -No!
I'm home already. No need.
Save those lovey-dovey eyes for your melodramas.
When did I ever give you lovey-dovey eyes?
I was just looking. You're the one who got butterflies.
As if!
I said go home. Go already!
Okay, Bo-bae. Calm down.
You need to calm down.
-I'm off. -Yeah, bye.
-Calm down, Bo-bae. -Yeah.
I'm calming down right now, Eun-ho. Bye.
I think he sometimes
forgets I've been single my whole life.
Damn.
Crap, my heart's still pounding.
That hurts.
Oh God.
Oh no! I'm bleeding!
It hurts.
Huh?
What?
Ms. Na Bo-bae?
Oh no. What if I just caused a blackout?
Damn it.
Click.
Pika.
Pikachu!
Why didn't it work?
What's going on?
Mr. Baek Ho-rang!
Huh?
Mr. Baek, did you fall?
Oh no. What do I do?
Mr. Baek Ho-rang, I'm coming!
Hold on.
Mr. Baek!
I'll…
Huh? Where is he?
Huh?
Here, right? Here!
Don't open it!
I told you not to come in!
-Are you hurt? Are you okay? -Ms. Na!
I'm not wearing anything right now!
I can't see anything anyway.
You're hurt.
Hold my hand. Can you see it?
Well, if I could, that'd be an even bigger problem!
Hey, there's a bathrobe over there. Just hand it to me.
-Bathrobe? -Yes, a bathrobe.
It's here.
Here.
-Here. Grab it. -Okay.
-Where is it? -Right here.
You reek of alcohol.
I'm sorry.
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang